(Sheldon:)Um, it's fairly technical.
(Priya:)I think I can handle it.
(Leonard:)Top of her class,
Cambridge University.
(Leonard:)Licensed to practice law
in three countries
(Leonard:)and your face.
(Priya:)All right,
based on a cursory reading,
(Priya:)it doesn't look like you have
much of a case, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Do so, do so.
(Priya:)Oh, I'm afraid not.
(Priya:)Section seven here, on
the right to enter the bathroom
(Priya:)in emergency situations,
is not specific
(Priya:)as to what constitutes
an emergency.
Oh, that's ridiculous!
(Sheldon:)A bathroom emergency
is self-explanatory.
(Priya:)Is it? If Leonard forgot
to trim his nose hair,
(Priya:)could he barge in
while you were showering?
(Sheldon:)Irrelevant. Leonard
doesn't trim his nose hair.
(Sheldon:)He thinks because he's short
nobody can see up there.
(Priya:)My point is, Sheldon,
the legal principle is,
(Priya:)ambiguity in a contract benefits
the party that did not draft it,